The Kirara Drive's main reactor has been damaged.
39% of the system is non-functional.
We're not taking off anytime soon.
Good grief. It's one thing after another.
Should we send a distress signal?
I'd like to, but the DES could discover our position again.
Basically, we're not going anywhere.
Not until the flying get us fixed.
What do we know about the planet?
I can't connect to the Archive.
We'll bring up any measurable data.
Gravity, 0.991.
Atmospheric composition, nitrogen, 78.2.
Oxygen, 21.1.
No toxic substances detected.
It's nice to have good news for a change.
Everyone, attention please.
We will now begin repairing the flying get.
To ensure our safety, you'll gather information on this planet.
The successors will scout using LAS.
The trainees will investigate the surrounding area.
It's possible you'll encounter the DES.
Be careful.
I'll help too.
Trainee Mikiko Minamino reporting in.
I'm pretty confident in my ability to pilot an LAS.
I'll do anything I can.
Just say the word, boss.
Mi-chan?
I think she's trying to atone for her sins.
The ship's interior could use a scrubbing.
You want me to clean?
Didn't you say you'd do anything?
Yeah.
All right.
What do we do now?
Repairing this ship is obvious.
But are we going to take back Akibastar?
Mm-hmm.
You can bug out.
Let's go.
Oh
I
We'll be right back.
So are you feeling any better, Makoto?
You betcha! Ready to go exploring!
That's what I like to hear.
Hey! Don't leave me behind!
Mushrooms, bamboo, shoot, tsuji no go!
You shouldn't touch mushrooms so indiscreetly, Sonati.
Oh! How cute!
Huh?
Ouch! That wasn't nice.
Linda, are you okay?
Yes. Tomorrow's your succession, so you'd better be careful.
Succession?
That's right. Everyone's here for your succession ceremony.
Congratulations on becoming the seventh generation white jelly mushroom!
Congratulations on your success, friend!
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you!
Linda, can we help you?
I hope you go to sleep right now!
What? Sonati?
Linda!
Ikuta!
I thought you were gonna die, you jerk!
Why are you crying?
I was having a strange dream and you woke me up.
Aww!
Why do my cheeks hurt so much?
No toxic substances.
Alright, now we won't get dehydrated.
Yeah.
Chiyori, I've seen that look before, thinking about your dad.
Sorry.
Because of my father, we were driven to a distant planet.
I've caused so much trouble.
It's not your fault.
I'm having fun.
It's like we're camping in a forest of mushrooms.
Nagisa, what should I do now?
I'll never let them use the Centernova for military purposes.
But I don't know how to stop my father, so what should I do?
Why don't you try facing him?
If you face your father head on,
there's a pretty good chance you might be able to change him.
My papa, I mean, my father,
he was strongly opposed to me becoming a member of Zero Zero.
But I knew what I wanted to do with my life.
So I became a trainee.
And now he supports me.
Well, I hope.
He sounds wonderful.
I'm jealous.
I'm sure your father's the same way.
Thanks, Nagisa.
It's these rainbow mushrooms again.
I'm beginning to think we've been going in circles.
Are you saying we might be lost out here?
What are we going to do?
Stop it right now.
When you're lost, you should keep calm and stay in one spot.
It's the golden rule of being lost.
Okay.
Well, that's what I always told my siblings when they would go outside to play.
It was my job to go find them.
And if they stayed in one spot, it was easy.
I didn't realize how uneasy it feels to be lost.
You're right.
We left Lancaster.
Now we've been driven from Akibastar.
We've come a long way since leaving home.
You're right.
But I only made it this far because of you and everyone else.
What?
I left the people I loved.
And faced all kinds of pain.
But Yuka, Nagisa, Chiri, we promised to join Zero Zero together.
I've been able to keep going because we've been pursuing that dream together.
But now, I wonder if we'll ever perform concerts again.
Of course we will.
Don't you even worry.
We'll take back Akibastar and be the DES.
You think so?
We'll all become successors too.
We'll all get new names, go to Lancaster, and perform for everyone.
All of us together.
Yeah, let's do it.
Mama!
That was Yuka and Orne.
Yuka, Orne!
Orne, don't breathe so quickly.
I'm trying.
Not again!
What is that?
A bug?
Dunno.
I'm not exactly sure what it is.
But it seems to be a native species of this planet.
Hey, what is that thing?
He fell out of the sky.
Does that taste good?
Oh yeah?
I can do that too!
Look, Orne has a fanboy.
Huh?
Either that or he thinks you're his mother.
His mother?
But I don't know how to be a mom.
What do I do?
Just act like yourself, silly.
That's pretty incredible.
It's hard to believe someone who just met you could get attached so quickly.
That's quite a gift.
I'm jealous.
But I didn't do anything.
Mofufu.
Huh?
That's a perfect name.
Because he's so fluffy.
Nice!
Welcome to the family, fluffy butt.
Nice to meet you, Mofufu.
Huh?
Huh? What the?
And they say I smell out.
Shut up.
It's a space monster!
Get back!
Mofaboo!
No! Mofaboo!
Arine! Arine! You can't go rushing out there!
That's right, it's too dangerous.
But I...
What are you going on about?
It's Arine! She says she's going to save Mofaboo!
You can't do that. Did you forget our predicament?
We're currently being pursued by the DES.
We'll be leaving this planet as soon as we finish repairing the Flying Get.
Don't take any unnecessary action until then.
But I...
I can't just leave him behind!
Arine!
Thank you.
Yeah.
Hm!
Huh.
That was great.
Close one. Don't squirm or anything.
Yuka!
Let's go. Mofufu's waiting for us.
Oh, girls. Thanks so much.
There he is.
Oh, no! Please!
Don't eat him!
Oh!
The DES!
No way!
How did they find us so quickly?
No. Those are machines that belong to Zodiac.
What?
Don't eat another dragon!
Please.
Oh, keep going.
They don't eat.
They don't eat all the things.
Ahhhhhhhhhh!
Ahhhhhhh!
It's for detecting Mofofu?
His mother.
Huh?
I think the big one is actually Mofofu's mother.
Ahhhhh!
Noooo!
Is everyone okay?
I'm trial trainee Mikiko Minamino.
I'm here on Chan Tsuba's orders.
Me, Chan-chan!
Good! You're all okay!
Yes, ma'am!
The Mopupoos!
Where do you think they're going?
Zero-zero-forty-eight interference?
That's impossible!
What are they doing way out here?
What?
This is Zodiac's mining planet?
That's right.
There's a good amount of Duolium here.
The fungis living in the forest are standing in their way of acquiring it.
Oh, so they…
Looks like the Archive is back online.
I found information on the fungis we saw.
Fungis are a life form that are unique to this planet.
Young fungis and adults look dramatically different from one another.
So Mopupoos is going to look like that someday?
Fungis are highly intelligent and live peacefully in the woods.
They are incredibly docile and almost never stray from their family packs.
That's all.
So then why are the peaceful fungis acting so ferociously and attacking us?
I don't blame them.
I'd be angry too if someone attacked my family.
They're taking baby fungis hostage to lure the big ones out of the forest.
That's awful!
Besides Mofufu, you're saying most of the children are gone?
Zodiac is harming the innocent fungis just to harvest resources for their industrial projects.
Epitheseus' enemies too.
To the fungis were despicable humans just like the people of Zodiac.
Look!
Oh!
Glow!
Whoa!
Mama!
It's a giant dualium crystal!
This must be what Zodiac is after.
Look at all the grown up fuzzies!
It looks like they're trying to heal themselves.
It's possible.
This dualium crystal may be a kind of sacred ground for the fungis populace.
I'm sorry.
We humans have done such terrible things to your home.
Tell us, how can we make it right?
Horine!
We can't let their own fuzzies go.
Oh!
We can't let them destroy another home!
I don't want any more sadness!
Losing a place you love hurts!
No matter who you are!
Let us fight to protect this place!
I'm sure that together we can find a way to beat Zodiac!
Loki!
Stop!
Listen!
We're not like the other humans!
We want to be your friends and help you!
I thought you said they were all intelligent!
Come along, come along, all the lonely follow me.
Feeling down won't bring you up, and it will not set you free.
That song!
They may be smart, but they're not human.
We can't expect them to understand language.
But if there's one thing we have, it's music!
Come on, come on!
You're lonely people.
You're falling asleep.
You don't have to worry about it.
Everyone, everyone, there's lots of fun.
Let's sing together.
Let's go!
투, 투…
嫌なことは、腹の底から
風船の中に吐き出そう
いっぱいいっぱい…膨らんできたら
ハリでついて、ファーッ!終わっちゃおう
Here's the sun
We're still ready and We're ready
Please let's get home
We'll sempre run
To me, you are not able to sail
I don't believe it! The fungies are singing with us!
It's amazing! They understand how we feel!
We've discovered a major dualium deposit!
We should harvest immediately!
Can you attack?
Not again!
osu!
What are you saying O what are you saying?
Of course nothing!
What's this?
Hihiya!
What's this? I'm reading increasing levels of Dualium and Kiratus in the area of the battle. You're sure about that?
The Dualium crystal! It's responding to your soul! I can feel it! The forest!
And everyone here! We're becoming one!
What's going on here? It's resonating with the Dualium and the Kirata Drive.
What did you say?
We're receiving a video from Takamina.
This glow! It's...
Could it be... Sensei-Sensei?
The Zodiac Attack drones have been driven back! A second assault on the forest would be impossible!
We did it!
That light was amazing! I could feel it!
Me too! It's like we were all connected by it!
Huh?
What? A crystal?
Fungi!
You're giving this to me?
Thank you!
Oh wow! I heard something!
Huh?
Like what?
The Fungi said, thank you to our new friends!
Yeah!
Oh wow! Awesome! Thank you too!
If we can communicate with Fungis...
Without using words...
Chiari?
We're retreating from this planet until backup arrives!
Hurry!
Chiari, what are you going to do?
Chiari!
Wait up!
I know this!
It's the same power we saw Chanyu use!
The Dualium Crystals must have responded to everyone's emotions.
By making the Kiraras shine brightly, they generated enough power to create a barrier and protect the Fungi's territory.
This is big. It could change everything.
If every member were capable of making Dualium resonate at maximum levels...
Taking back Akibastar may not be a dream.
Tsubasa-san!
We can't find Chiari or Nagisa anywhere!
Chiari...
What do you think you're doing?
If I'm right, this ship is probably returning to Sagittarius star in Zodiac.
Huh?
I'm doing what you told me.
I'm going...to face my father.
I fall?
Please, my family!
Would you dare hate your desire to raise your Engineering program?
Maybe it's not true...
It will get then.
No…
What?
I don't know!
No…
We see...
It will durante...
And that it will catch all of us...
Coming up...
Looks like a delt...
How...
In the lifetime...
Awesome.
We.
Have a three minutes to join our Simploresce...
To this eventual ברcria...
Did we find all of our peace?
And sometimes the moment You'll seed juice
Thisulously bad me A treasure for you
Make it look you very nella
So many others They're under no observe
At the sky I'm fyummer
I'll come to fall rain
Oh, I want you to help me
I can led this to this
겠어요 of your shyness
This is where Chie-Ri was born
I think Chiari must want to settle things with her father.
Come, show me your shine, my daughter.
Nagisa, I'm going to face my father.